Guide to the Hapgood Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1893-1977; Series III; 9.5; (23 boxes)
  - HUTCHINS HAPGOOD
    - Shorter Works
      - Essays
        - "An Aristocrat": holograph, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 838)
        - "Are You Interested in Christianity?": typescript and carbon, corrected with notes (Box 28, Folder 839)
        - "A Civilized Wanderer: 'Cigarette,' the Tramp": holograph (Box 28, Folder 840)
        - "The Columbia Conserve Co.": typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 841)
        - "Democracy in Prison": holograph, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 842)
        - "The Dignity of Madness": holograph, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 843)
        - "The Dollar": holograph, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 844)
        - "Dostoevski and the Revolution": holograph (Box 28, Folder 845)
        - "The Drama of the Italians"
          - Holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 846)
          - Typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 847)
        - "Emma Goldman": typescript, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 848)
        - "George W. Perkins": typescript, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 849)
        - "Germans": typescript, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 850)
        - Germany, Essays on
          - 1. "The Fate of the Middle-class": holograph and typescript (Box 28, Folder 851)
          - 2. "A German Professor": holograph and typescript (Box 28, Folder 852)
          - 3. "A German Student": holograph and typescript (Box 28, Folder 853)
          - 4. "Free Speech in Berlin": holograph and typescript (Box 28, Folder 854)
          - 5. "My German Brother": holograph and typescript (Box 28, Folder 855)
          - 6. "One of Many": holograph and typescript (Box 28, Folder 856)
          - 7. "Freiburg": holograph and typescript (Box 28, Folder 857)
          - Miscellaneous draft fragments, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 858)
        - "A Good Citizen--Emma Goldman": holograph with draft fragments, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 859)
        - "Hamlet": holograph, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 860)
        - "In Memoriam" [re Virginia Myers]: printed version, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 861)
        - "The Italians"
          - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 862)
          - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 863)
        - "The New Bohemia": holograph, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 864)
        - "The New Pilgrims Progress": holograph, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 865)
        - "An Old American Replies to Charles Lindbergh"
          - Typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 866)
          - Draft fragments, typescript, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 867)
        - "Oliver Chaffee": typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 868)
        - "On Prohibition": holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 869)
        - "On Respectability"
          - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 870)
          - Draft B, holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 871)
        - "Open-mindedness of Editors": holograph (Box 29, Folder 872)
        - "The Penetentiary at Volterra": holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 873)
        - "A Perverse Poet": typescript, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 874)
        - "The Provincetown Players": holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 875)
        - "Radicalism in Art"
          - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 876)
          - Draft B, holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 877)
          - Draft C, holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 878)
          - Draft fragments, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 879)
        - "The Saloon As a Social Centre"
          - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 880)
          - Draft B, holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 881)
        - "The Scourge of God": typescript, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 882)
        - "Senator Nelson": holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 883)
        - "Sidney West": holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 884)
        - "Since Gordon Died": holograph, corrected (Box 29, Folder 885)
        - "The Spring": typescript, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 886)
        - "The Third Day": holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 887)
        - "To the Reasoning Nature of Man": holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 888)
        - "The Twilight of the War": holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 889)
        - "Two Dreams": holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 890)
        - "The Voice of Shakespeare": typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 891)
        - "The War"
          - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 892)
          - Draft B, holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 893)
          - Draft fragments, holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 894)
        - "What Is an Anarchist?": holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 895)
        - "Why Any Man Should Not Marry a Suffragette": typescript, carbon, 1910 Dec 22 (Box 29, Folder 896)
        - "Will Hitler Attack the Soviet Union?": typescript, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 897)
        - "The Youth of Italy"
          - Holograph, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 898)
          - Typescript, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 899)
        - Miscellaneous draft fragments, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 900)
      - Letters to the Editor, 1913-46, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 901)
  - NEITH BOYCE HAPGOOD
    Materials in the Neith Boyce Hapgood subseries are divided into four subseries, Books, Plays, Poems, and Shorter Works, and are arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Books
      - Bibliography, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 902)
      - "Autobiography"
        - Research notes, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 903)
        - Draft A, holograph and typescript (Box 30, Folder 904-07)
        - Draft B, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 908-11)
        - Draft C, typescript, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 912-15)
      - "The Debtor"
        - Holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 916-21)
        - Holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 922-26)
        - Draft fragments, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 927)
      - "The Doomed City"
        - Research notes, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 928)
        - Draft A, typescript, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 929)
        - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 930-31)
        - Draft C, typescript, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 932)
        - Draft D, typescript, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 933)
        - Draft E, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 934-35)
        - Draft E, fragments, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 936)
        - Draft F, typescript, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 937)
        - Draft G, typescript, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 938)
        - Draft H, typescript, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 939-40)
        - Draft fragments, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 941)
        - Draft fragments, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 942-45)
      - "Grey Mares"
        - Typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 946)
        - Draft fragments, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 947-55)
      - Harry: A Portrait
        - Book reviews, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 956)
        - Contract, 1923 Apr 17 (Box 32, Folder 957)
      - Proud Lady
        - Advertisements, ca. 1923 (Box 32, Folder 958)
        - Book reviews, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 959)
      - The Story of an American Family
        - Draft A, typescript, carbon, parts I-V, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 960-64)
        - Draft A, typescript, carbon, parts VI-XVI, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 965-75)
        - Draft B, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 976-81)
        - Draft B, fragments, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 982)
      - "The Town in the Forest"
        - Research notes, parts I-III, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 983-85)
        - Research notes written on discarded pages of MSS of novel about Estelle Langdon (Box 34, Folder 986)
        - Draft A (verse version), typescript, corrected, parts I-II, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 987-88)
        - Draft B (verse version), typescript, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 989-90)
        - Ch. I, "'Activity,'" draft fragments, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 991)
        - Ch. II, "The First Settlers," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, parts I-II, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 992-93)
        - Ch. III, "Heritage," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, parts I-III, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 994-96)
        - Ch. IV, "The King's Woods," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, parts I-III, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 997-99)
        - Ch. V, "The First Town Meetings," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, parts I-III, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1000-02)
        - Ch. VI, "The Revolution," draft fragments, typescript, corrected (Box 35, Folder 1003)
        - Ch. VII, "Short Annals of the Poor," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1004)
        - Ch. VIII, "Richmond Secedes to Vermont," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, parts I-II (Box 35, Folder 1005-06)
        - Ch. IX, "General Washington Intervenes," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1007)
        - Ch. X, "Richmond Returns to Its Muttons," draft fragments, typescript, corrected (Box 35, Folder 1008)
        - Ch. XI, "'Friends' in the Forest," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, parts I-III (Box 35, Folder 1009-11)
        - Ch. XII, "The Ballous in Richmond," draft fragments, typescript, corrected (Box 35, Folder 1012)
        - Ch. XIII, "Winter Scene," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, parts I-III, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1013-15)
        - Ch. XIV, "The Town in 1806," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1016)
        - Ch. XV, "Apogee," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1017)
        - Ch. XVI, "The Rich Forties," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1018)
        - Ch. XVII, "Arts and Letters in Richmond," draft fragments, typescript, corrected (Box 36, Folder 1019)
        - Ch. XVIII, "Autumn Decades," draft fragments, typescript, corrected (Box 36, Folder 1020)
        - Ch. XIX, "Richmond Today," draft fragments, typescript, corrected, parts I-II (Box 36, Folder 1021-22)
        - "Appendix," draft fragments, typescript, corrected (Box 36, Folder 1023)
        - Draft C, typescript, photocopy, edited from earlier drafts by Beatrix Hapgood Faust, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1024-28)
        - Draft fragments, holograph and typescript, corrected, parts I-VIII (Box 36, Folder 1029-36)
    - Plays
      - List of plays with names of major characters, partial, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1037)
      - "The Adventurers": outline, holograph, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1038)
      - "All in the Family"
        - Draft A, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1039)
        - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1040)
        - Draft fragments, holograph, and typescript, corrected (Box 37, Folder 1041)
      - "The Bark and the Tree"
        - Draft A, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1042)
        - Draft B, typescript and carbon (Box 37, Folder 1043)
      - "Beatrix Esmond": typescript and carbon (Box 37, Folder 1044)
      - "The Blind"
        - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1045-46)
        - Draft B, holograph, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1047)
        - Draft C, holograph, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1048)
      - The Bond: royalties, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 1049)
      - "Dead Men's Shoes"
        - Act I, draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1050)
        - Act II, draft, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1051)
        - Act III, draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1052)
        - Draft fragments, parts I-VII, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1053-59)
      - "An Eveless Eden": draft, typescript, carbon (Box 37, Folder 1060)
      - "The Faithful Lover"
        - Draft A, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1061)
        - Draft B, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1062)
        - Draft C, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1063)
        - Draft D, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1064)
      - "Forgiveness": outline, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1065)
      - "Forty": sketch, holograph, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1066)
      - "The Handicap"
        - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1067)
        - Draft B, holograph, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1068)
      - "Hurricane"
        - Draft A, typescript, corrected and carbon, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 1069)
        - Draft B, typescript, carbon, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 1070)
        - Draft C, typescript, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 1071)
        - Draft fragments, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 1072)
      - "The Lowestoft Cup"
        - Draft A, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1073)
        - Draft B, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1074)
      - "The Old Dominion": draft fragments, typescript, part I-III (Box 38, Folder 1075-77)
      - "The Oyster"
        - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1078)
        - Draft B, holograph, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1079)
      - "The Primrose Path"
        - Draft A, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1080)
        - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1081)
      - "Profane Love": outline, typescript, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1082)
      - "The Sea Lady"
        - Draft A, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1083)
        - Draft B, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1084-85)
      - "The Shadow": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1086)
      - "The Sire de Maletroit's Door": draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1087)
      - "Spring"
        - Draft A, typescript, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1088)
        - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1089)
        - Draft B, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1090)
      - "Tradition": draft fragments, parts I-IV (Box 38, Folder 1091-94)
      - "A True Woman": outline, holograph, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1095)
      - The Two Sons
        - Publicity, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1096)
        - Royalties, 1921 May 28 (Box 38, Folder 1097)
      - "Winchester's History in a Pageant": draft, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1098)
      - "Winter's Night"
        - Draft A, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1099)
        - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1100)
        - Draft C, typescript, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1101)
      - Unidentified: draft, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1102)
      - Miscellaneous draft fragments, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1103)
    - Poems
      - "After Sunset": printed version, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1104)
      - "Against the far faint blue of distant sky...": draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1105)
      - "L'amour est mon premier..." and "Mon premier est là-dedans...": drafts, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1106)
      - "Arbutus," "The Bluebird," and "Sentinels": drafts, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1107)
      - "At the Grave": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1108)
      - "Beatrix": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1109)
      - "Beauty is hers--long fluent line of grace...": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1110)
      - "Dawn near Monhegan": draft, typescript (Box 39, Folder 1111)
      - "Earthly Troubles and Quarrels": draft, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1112)
      - "England!"
        - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1113)
        - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1114)
      - "Fiore de mela...": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1115)
      - "Give me the burning sun and the burnt white ground...": draft, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1116)
      - "The hills, a symphony of blue...": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1117)
      - "Hutch": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1118)
      - "i do not;": draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1119)
      - "In the Library": draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1120)
      - "Look back, look back...": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1121)
      - "The Mermaid": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1122)
      - "Morrina": printed version, 1893 Sep (Box 39, Folder 1123)
      - "Noël": printed version, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1124)
      - "O Moon," "Shining Out," "Boabdil," and "The Trail": drafts, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1125)
      - "A Raga" and "Prayer Song": drafts, typescript (Box 39, Folder 1126)
      - "Rain Drops" and "The Wolves": drafts, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1127)
      - "Sing thou of summer's splendor and the sun...": draft, typescript (Box 39, Folder 1128)
      - "The Song of Cowskin Joe": draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1129)
      - "The Storm," "Flying," "Sounds," "Who Dares," and "Song": drafts, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1130)
      - "Summer Night": draft, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1131)
      - "Three Desert Songs," i.e. "Sunset," "Night," and "Dawn": drafts, typescript, corrected (Box 39, Folder 1132)
      - "To H. H. at 50": draft, holograph, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 1133)
      - "To H. H. at Forty": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1134)
      - "To H. H. at 46": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1135)
      - "To Mother": draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1136)
      - "A Villein [?] I Know," "Thanks," and "Between Us": draft, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1137)
      - "The Waves," "Out to the Edge of the Floe," and "In Old Japan": drafts, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1138)
      - "What I See": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1139)
    - Shorter Works
      - Book reviews
        See also: Oversize, Box 48, folder 1538
        - List of book reviews, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1140)
        - "Books," review of Lawrence, D. H., Sons and Lovers and Herrick, Robert, Clark's Field: draft, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1141)
        - "Books and Men," in Harper's Weekly, review of Herrick, Robert, Clark's Field; Dunn, Robert, The Youngest World; Reed, John, Insurgent Mexico; London, Jack, The Mutiny of the Elsinore; Sedgwick, Anne Douglas, The Encounter; Sinclair, May, "Three Sisters"; Atherton, Gertrude, Perch of the Devil: printed version, 1914 Dec 5 (Box 39, Folder 1142)
        - "The Eternal Feminist," in The New Republic, review of Herrick, Robert, The End of Desire: printed version (Box 39, Folder 1143)
      - Essays
        "Bring on Your Rubber-tired Hack"
        - Draft A, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1144)
        - Draft B, typescript and carbon (Box 39, Folder 1145)
        - "The Fate of an Old Town"
          - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1146)
          - Draft B, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1147)
        - "A Few Siamese Cats"
          - Draft A, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1148)
          - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1149)
        - "Gardens": draft, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1150)
        - "Harry": draft, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1151)
        - "A Homeric Epic of Illinois": draft, draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1152)
        - "House on the Mountain": draft, typescript (Box 39, Folder 1153)
        - "Hurricane in New Hampshire"
          - Draft A, typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1154)
          - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1155)
        - "Iowa to Delphi": draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1156)
        - "Knowing People": draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1157)
        - "Labor--the American People": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1158)
        - "Middle Age: A Proposal to Make War Rational": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1159)
        - "My Wild Garden": draft, typescript, and carbon (Box 39, Folder 1160)
        - "Natural Selection": draft, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1161)
        - "Our Disillusion"
          - Outline, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1162)
          - Draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1163)
        - "Our Neighbor's Dog": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1164)
        - "The Perfumed Beggar"
          - Draft A, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1165)
          - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1166)
        - "Proud Lady: Portrait of a Puritan": draft, holograph (Box 39, Folder 1167)
        - "Rainbow's End": draft, typescript, corrected (Box 39, Folder 1168)
        - "The 'Regie' Murder Case": draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1169)
        - "Skirts": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1170)
        - "Slightly to the Left of Paradise"
          - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1171)
          - Draft B, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1172)
        - "Tribute": draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1173)
        - "Vadsoe of Norway"
          - Draft A, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1174)
          - Draft B, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1175)
        - "A Vermont Winter": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1176)
        - "What Have You in Your Town?": draft, typescript (Box 39, Folder 1177)
        - "Young Soldier of the Republic, 1861-1865"
          - Draft A, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1178)
          - Draft B, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1179)
        - Unidentified: draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1180)
      - Letters to the Editor
        - Letters to the Editor, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1181)
      - Short Stories
        - List of short stories with names of major characters, partial, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1182)
        - "Afterward": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1183)
        - "The Agent"
          - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1184)
          - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1185)
          - Draft C, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1186)
        - "Agnes and Rosamunde"
          - Draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1187)
          - Draft, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1188)
          - Draft fragments, holograph, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1189)
        - "Ambrotype"
          - Draft A, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1190)
          - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1191)
          - Draft C, typescript, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1192)
        - "Apron Strings"
          - Draft A, typescript, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1193)
          - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1194)
        - "Art and Woman": draft, typescript, corrected (Box 40, Folder 1195)
        - "The Artist": draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1196)
        - "At Sea"
          - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1197)
          - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1198)
        - "Aunts Millicent and Jane": draft, typescript (Box 40, Folder 1199)
        - "The Blue Pearl": printed version, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1200)
        - "The Bottle": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1201)
        - "The Bride's Dress": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1202)
        - "Bringing Gifts": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1203)
        - "A British Matron": printed version (incomplete), 1914 Dec 19 (Box 40, Folder 1204)
        - "The Brothers": printed version, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1205)
        - "The Canary": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1206)
        - "The Careful Lover": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1207)
        - "The Centaur": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1208)
        - "The Chinese Panel"
          - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1209)
          - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1210)
        - "The Chinese Ring": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1211)
        - "The Citadel": outline and draft, holograph (Box 40, Folder 1212)
        - "Concha and Luis": draft, holograph (Box 40, Folder 1213)
        - "The Convert": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1214)
        - "A Dash and Some Asterisks": draft, typescript (Box 40, Folder 1215)
        - "Derelict"
          - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1216)
          - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1217)
        - "The Dumb Wife": draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1218)
        - "Easy Street": draft, holograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1219)
        - "The Elder Generation": printed version, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1220)
        - "Emily"
          - Draft A, typescript, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1221)
          - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1222)
          - Draft fragments, holograph and typescript (Box 40, Folder 1223)
        - "The Eternal Flame"